<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Using on Currency</title>
    <link>https://billthefarmer.github.io/currency/using/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Using on Currency</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <copyright>Copyright &amp;copy; 2021 Bill Farmer</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 04 Mar 2020 10:18:47 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://billthefarmer.github.io/currency/using/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Edit</title>
      <link>https://billthefarmer.github.io/currency/using/edit/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Mar 2020 10:20:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://billthefarmer.github.io/currency/using/edit/</guid>
      <description>Touch the current currency value field to edit the value. The display will be updated dynamically as you type. Touch the Done button on the numeric keypad to update the value field. The whole value field is selected by default when touched so it will be overwritten by typing in a new value. To deselect the text, touch an adjacent area, like the currency flag.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Toolbar</title>
      <link>https://billthefarmer.github.io/currency/using/toolbar/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Mar 2020 10:20:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://billthefarmer.github.io/currency/using/toolbar/</guid>
      <description>The icons in the toolbar are:
 Add a currency to the list. A scrollable list of currencies will pop up. Touch an entry to add it or touch the Cancel button below the list. Long touch an entry to select it. Once one currency is selected others may be added or removed from the selection by touching them. Another long touch on another currency will clear the list and select the new currency.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Edit Currency List</title>
      <link>https://billthefarmer.github.io/currency/using/edit-list/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Mar 2020 10:29:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://billthefarmer.github.io/currency/using/edit-list/</guid>
      <description>Touch a currency entry in the list to make it current. The old current currency will move to the top of the list. Long touch a currency entry to select it. Once one currency is selected others may be added or removed from the selection by touching them. Another long touch on another currency will clear the list and select the new currency. The icons in the toolbar will change to:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chart</title>
      <link>https://billthefarmer.github.io/currency/using/chart/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Mar 2020 10:30:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://billthefarmer.github.io/currency/using/chart/</guid>
      <description>The display shows an interactive chart of the last 90 days of historical rates from the ECB. The chart responds to two finger pinch and expand gestures and will scroll once expanded. The toolbar icons from left to right are:
 Invert the chart. New chart The scrollable list of currencies will pop up. Select one or two currencies from the list as above to replace the current currencies in the chart.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
